mondseetage.com 2019-02-06

# Privacy Policy – fofoshoes

We respect your privacy and understand the importance of protecting your personal information. Maintaining your privacy and trust is very important to Starryou.com. Please contact our Customer Service team [service@fofoshoes.com](mailto:service@fofoshoes.com) if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy.

### What /when personal information do we collect from the people that visit Fofoshoes.com?

When ordering or register on our website, we will collect your name, billing and delivery address, your e-mail address, and your purchase/return/exchange information.

### We will use your personal information in the following ways:

To fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, or requests for information, subscribe to a newsletter.

To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions

To help us learn more about your shopping preferences

To contact you if necessary

### Do we use cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users in the aggregate by analyzing popular areas and products to enhance future experiences on our site. Cookies do not cause damage to your computer systems or files, and only the web site that transferred a particular cookie to you can read, modify or delete such cookie. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there are simple procedures in most browsers that allow you to delete existing cookies, to automatically decline cookies, or to be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer of particular cookies to your computer.

### Third Party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. Also, we do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Newsletters

Newsletter will be sent out regularly, with the latest updates on new arrivals, recent hottest deals, special offers and bargains, as well as the exclusive coupons and discounts to our email subscribers. We respect your privacy and will not disclose your details to any third party. You can contact our customer service to unsubscribe at any time.

### Security

mondseetage.com takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the Secure Socket Layers (SSLs) encryption software. SSL encrypts your own information, so only we are able to decode the information.

However, security systems are not infallible, including encryption systems. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We ask all our customers to take measures to help protect information in their online accounts, including the following:

Install the latest security updates and anti-virus software on your computer to help prevent malware and viruses.

Reset your e-mail account passwords frequently.

Use complex passwords (a minimum of 6 alpha/numeric letters).

Do not use the same password on more than one website.

Do not share your password with others.

If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for private information, do not respond. Cause we will never request your password, credit card information or other information through e-mail

### Changes to This Policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the site, without prior notice. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Internet, accessible through the site. Use of the site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised policy then in effect.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

* This page was last updated on 20 June. 2018
